<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybertruck.dev - A Tesla Cybertruck Dev Site! </title>
    <description>A Cybertruck Dev page!</description>
    <link>https://cybertruck.dev/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://cybertruck.dev/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 13:34:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Battery Revolution - Understanding Tesla's Advancements in Energy Storage</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Interested in a Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla is a name synonymous with groundbreaking electric vehicles (EVs), but what often gets overshadowed is the company’s pioneering role in battery technology. While the sleek designs and autonomous driving features grab headlines, it’s Tesla’s advancements in energy storage that truly set it apart. Let’s delve into the technological breakthroughs that enable Tesla’s industry-leading range and what the future holds for battery technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-brief-history-of-tesla-batteries&quot;&gt;A Brief History of Tesla Batteries&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Tesla introduced the Roadster back in 2008, it was powered by thousands of small lithium-ion cells, similar to those found in laptops. This was a radical departure from the large, custom-made battery packs that were common in EVs at that time. Tesla’s innovative approach allowed for better energy density, greater range, and more flexible design options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-lithium-ion-paradigm&quot;&gt;The Lithium-Ion Paradigm&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s commitment to lithium-ion technology has been a key factor in its success. The energy density of lithium-ion batteries allows Tesla vehicles to achieve impressive ranges that often exceed 300 miles on a single charge. Moreover, lithium-ion batteries are lighter and more compact than other battery types, which contributes to the overall performance and efficiency of Tesla cars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;enter-the-gigafactory&quot;&gt;Enter the Gigafactory&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To meet its ambitious production targets and bring down the cost of batteries, Tesla established its Gigafactories. These massive facilities aim to produce enough batteries to power 500,000 vehicles annually. The scale of these operations has not only allowed Tesla to reduce the cost per kilowatt-hour (kWh) but has also facilitated advancements in battery chemistry and architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;battery-management-system-bms&quot;&gt;Battery Management System (BMS)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One often-overlooked aspect of Tesla’s battery innovation is its Battery Management System (BMS). The BMS is software that regulates various parameters like voltage, temperature, and charge/discharge rates. This ensures optimal performance and longevity, further setting Tesla batteries apart from the competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cutting-edge-innovations-4680-cells-and-beyond&quot;&gt;Cutting-Edge Innovations: 4680 Cells and Beyond&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s Battery Day in 2020 unveiled the new 4680 cells, which promise five times more energy storage, six times more power, and a 16% increase in range compared to their existing cells. These cells are expected to be a game-changer in the EV industry, making electric cars more affordable and extending their range significantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-future-solid-state-batteries-and-more&quot;&gt;The Future: Solid-State Batteries and More&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Tesla has made significant advancements in lithium-ion technology, the future might hold even more revolutionary changes. Solid-state batteries, which promise higher energy density and faster charging times, could be the next frontier. Tesla is already researching this technology, and it could become another leap forward in energy storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s achievements in battery technology are arguably as groundbreaking as their most iconic cars. As the company continues to innovate, the ripple effects are felt not just in the automotive industry, but in the broader push toward sustainable energy solutions. Whether it’s the mass production of more efficient lithium-ion cells or the exploration of cutting-edge technologies like solid-state batteries, Tesla’s battery revolution shows no signs of slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Interested in a Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/battery-revolution</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/battery-revolution</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Industry</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Tesla Revolutionized the Automotive Industry</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Interested in a Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the annals of automotive history, few companies have ignited as much change, debate, and excitement as Tesla. Founded in 2003 by Martin Eberhard and Marc Tarpenning, and later joined by Elon Musk, Ian Wright, and JB Straubel, Tesla Inc. set out with a daring goal: to prove that electric vehicles (EVs) could be better than gasoline-powered cars. Over the years, Tesla has not only achieved this but has spurred a series of innovations that have reshaped the industry at large. Here’s a look at how Tesla has revolutionized the automotive realm:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-emphasis-on-electric&quot;&gt;1. Emphasis on Electric:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s singular focus on EVs challenged the long-standing assumption that electric cars were impractical or inferior to traditional combustion engine vehicles. With the launch of the Roadster in 2008, Tesla demonstrated that EVs could be both high-performance and desirable. This shift in perception led many traditional automakers to accelerate their EV programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-direct-to-consumer-sales-model&quot;&gt;2. Direct-to-Consumer Sales Model:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bypassing the traditional dealership system, Tesla opted for a direct sales model. Customers visit Tesla showrooms or order their cars online. This approach has given Tesla tighter control over its sales experience and branding, while also raising legal and legislative debates in various states over automotive sales laws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-supercharger-network&quot;&gt;3. Supercharger Network:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest concerns with EVs has always been “range anxiety” – the fear that an electric vehicle would run out of power before reaching a charging station. Tesla’s answer was the Supercharger network, a series of high-speed charging stations that not only charge Tesla vehicles quickly but are also strategically placed to allow for long-distance travel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-over-the-air-updates&quot;&gt;4. Over-the-Air Updates:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While software updates in traditional vehicles often require a trip to the dealership, Tesla’s EVs can be updated remotely, much like a smartphone. These over-the-air updates can enhance performance, rectify issues, or even add entirely new features, ensuring that vehicles improve after they’ve been purchased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-self-driving-ambitions&quot;&gt;5. Self-Driving Ambitions:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autopilot, Tesla’s advanced driver assistance system, brought semi-autonomous driving capabilities to the mainstream. While not fully self-driving, the system incorporates features like lane-keeping, adaptive cruise control, and automated parking. Tesla’s commitment to a self-driving future has pushed other automakers to fast-track their autonomous driving programs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-gigafactories-and-vertical-integration&quot;&gt;6. Gigafactories and Vertical Integration:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To support its ambitious EV production targets, Tesla has invested in large-scale manufacturing plants known as Gigafactories. These massive facilities, found in locations from Nevada to Shanghai, represent Tesla’s commitment to vertical integration and aim to drive down the costs of batteries and EV production.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-open-source-patents&quot;&gt;7. Open-Source Patents:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2014, Elon Musk announced that Tesla would make its electric car patents available to the public and allow others to use them in good faith. This unprecedented move was intended to foster innovation in the EV space and accelerate the global transition to sustainable transport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;8-emphasis-on-sustainability&quot;&gt;8. Emphasis on Sustainability:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s mission is not just about producing EVs, but promoting sustainable energy more broadly. Their solar products, energy storage solutions (like the Powerwall and Powerpack), and even their acquisition of SolarCity, underscore a broader vision for a sustainable energy ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s journey from an EV start-up to a major automotive powerhouse is a testament to its audacious vision and its ability to disrupt established norms. While the company has faced its share of challenges and criticisms, its impact on the automotive industry is undeniable. As major automakers pivot to electric and sustainable models, much of that momentum can be attributed to the trail that Tesla blazed. Whether one is an avid supporter or a skeptic, the Tesla story offers invaluable lessons on innovation, persistence, and the power of vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Interested in a Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/tesla-auto-industry</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/tesla-auto-industry</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Industry</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>From Gasoline to Gigawatts- Why Switch to a Tesla?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Interested in a Tesla?&lt;/a&gt;
If you’re still driving that trusty old gas-powered vehicle, you might be wondering why there’s so much buzz about electric vehicles (EVs), particularly those from Tesla. Should you consider making the leap to electric? Let’s delve into the reasons why many are opting for the Tesla experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-environmental-benefits&quot;&gt;1. Environmental Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;reduced-emissions&quot;&gt;Reduced Emissions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional gasoline vehicles emit a significant amount of pollutants, contributing to air pollution and climate change. Tesla vehicles, being 100% electric, have zero tailpipe emissions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;clean-energy-transition&quot;&gt;Clean Energy Transition&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If charged with renewable energy sources like wind or solar, Tesla cars operate entirely on clean energy, further reducing your carbon footprint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-economic-advantages&quot;&gt;2. Economic Advantages&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;lower-operating-costs&quot;&gt;Lower Operating Costs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Electricity, on a per-mile basis, is generally cheaper than gasoline. Additionally, with fewer moving parts compared to traditional vehicles, EVs often have lower maintenance costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;federal-and-state-incentives&quot;&gt;Federal and State Incentives&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Governments around the world offer incentives to EV owners, ranging from tax credits to rebates and carpool lane access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-advanced-technology&quot;&gt;3. Advanced Technology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;autopilot--full-self-driving&quot;&gt;Autopilot &amp;amp; Full Self-Driving&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla is at the forefront of autonomous driving technology. Their advanced driver-assistance system, Autopilot, is included standard, and with additional upgrades, the potential for full self-driving becomes a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;over-the-air-updates&quot;&gt;Over-the-Air Updates&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla vehicles receive regular software updates over the air, bringing improvements and new features directly to the car without needing a trip to a service center.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-superior-performance&quot;&gt;4. Superior Performance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla EVs are known for their impressive acceleration and top speeds. The instant torque provided by electric motors gives a driving experience unlike any gasoline-powered sports car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-the-supercharger-network&quot;&gt;5. The Supercharger Network&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla’s expanding Supercharger network makes long-distance travel easy. Charging stops are faster than ever, and the integrated navigation in Tesla vehicles plans the route and charging stops for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-future-proofing&quot;&gt;6. Future-Proofing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The auto industry is experiencing a seismic shift towards electrification. As more cities consider banning or restricting gasoline cars, owning an EV, especially from a brand as forward-thinking as Tesla, ensures you’re future-proofed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-a-holistic-experience&quot;&gt;7. A Holistic Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tesla is more than just a car manufacturer. From their solar products to energy storage solutions, the brand is paving the way for a sustainable future. By owning a Tesla, you become part of this vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Switching from a gasoline vehicle to a Tesla is not just about joining a trend; it’s about embracing the future. It’s about aligning with a sustainable vision, benefiting from cutting-edge technology, and enjoying an unrivaled driving experience. As the world heads toward cleaner energy solutions, now might be the perfect time to make the transition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ts.la/christopher30216&quot;&gt;Be sure to buy your Tesla via our link!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/gasoline-to-gigawatts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/gasoline-to-gigawatts</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Electric</category>
        
        <category>Industry</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to tell your Cybertruck Order Number Position</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So you’ve ordered a Cybertruck, and you’re wondering how many people are ahead of you in line.  Here’s how to tell:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tesla.com/cybertruck&quot;&gt;Tesla’s Cybertruck Order Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “Manage” in the upper right corner&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “View Details” next to your Cybertruck order&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “View Order Agreement”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Search for “Order Number” in the document&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your order number will be in the format RN123456789&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what does that tell you? Not a whole lot without a little more info, so here you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/view/tesla-reservation-tracker&quot;&gt;Cybertruck Reservation Tracker&lt;/a&gt;, it will provide you some info, but the value is limited because some of the data is just flat out wrong. My order for example, says it is attached to someone in Ithaca, NY and is a prior Tesla Owner. I am in Missouri, and have never owned a Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That tracker shows that my order is estimated to be position 6,368, and 1,338 in line for the Trim (3 motor) that I ordered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also a bunch of duplicate order numbers in there with all sorts of different order dates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So trying to throw out most of their filtering logic based on the assumption that they simply don’t have the right info, let’s start with a more basic assumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Order number 112,744,133 shows up with a “corrected” position of 9, so let’s assume that the order number is within 13-15 numbers of that actual order number, so somewhere around 112,744,120. That puts my order number around 7,080.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tracker tries to estimate out how many “other” orders (other models, not truck) were placed for Teslas in between when the initial order was placed, and my Cybertruck order was placed. I have a hard time believing that many, if any, were ordering other Teslas in the few minutes from the time the order window opened to the time that I ordered, so I would lean towards somewhere in that 7k range for my order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the question is how many folks will cancel their Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many people have already cancelled their Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many people will simply not respond when the order banks actually open up and people need to start configuring the paying for their Cybertruck?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we near the end of Q3 2023, my uneducated assumptions tell me that we will see some pricing and delivery of the Cybertruck before the end of September 2023, and from there we will see production ramp up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am expecting to get to place my order sometime in late Spring 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all based on a lot of assumptions. My last vehicle order, a Ford F250, took 400 days from the day I ordered it to the date I picked it up, and that wasn’t a NEW model, it was just a super duty truck from Ford….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When do you think you’ll get your Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-ordernumber</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-ordernumber</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cybertruck's Arrival in Missouri - A New Chapter in Automotive Innovation</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-cybertrucks-arrival-in-missouri-a-new-chapter-in-automotive-innovation&quot;&gt;The Cybertruck’s Arrival in Missouri: A New Chapter in Automotive Innovation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missouri, long known for its contributions to the automotive industry, is soon to become one of the latest states to welcome Tesla’s futuristic electric vehicle, the Cybertruck. Set to disrupt the trucking market with its radical design and cutting-edge technology, the Cybertruck is poised to make a significant impact in the Show-Me State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;teslas-cybertruck-a-quick-overview&quot;&gt;Tesla’s Cybertruck: A Quick Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cybertruck, announced by Tesla in 2019, is a fully electric pickup truck that challenges the conventional automotive design. With its angular, stainless steel exterior and innovative electric drivetrain, the Cybertruck has captured the imagination of auto enthusiasts and tech-savvy consumers alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featuring a 100 cubic feet of exterior, lockable storage, the Cybertruck aims to provide utility and performance without compromising on environmental sustainability. With different models offering a range of up to 500 miles on a single charge and the ability to tow over 14,000 pounds, it is seen as a serious competitor to traditional fossil fuel-powered trucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;missouris-automotive-history&quot;&gt;Missouri’s Automotive History&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missouri has a rich history in the automotive industry. Kansas City and St. Louis have been home to several major car manufacturing plants, contributing significantly to the economy and technological development in the area. The arrival of the Cybertruck is seen as a continuation of this tradition, marking a new era of innovation and progress in automotive manufacturing and electric vehicle adoption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-demand-for-electric-vehicles-in-missouri&quot;&gt;The Demand for Electric Vehicles in Missouri&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent years, Missouri has seen a growing interest in electric vehicles (EVs). The state government has been proactive in supporting EV adoption through incentives, charging infrastructure, and collaboration with industry leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Cybertruck’s arrival, there is anticipation for a surge in consumer interest in electric trucks, particularly among those involved in agriculture, construction, and other industries that rely heavily on pickup trucks. The Cybertruck’s blend of power and efficiency is expected to appeal to a wide range of consumers across the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;economic-impact&quot;&gt;Economic Impact&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The introduction of the Cybertruck to Missouri may also have significant economic implications. Beyond the consumer market, the Cybertruck may find applications in various commercial sectors, potentially generating new business opportunities and jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local dealerships and service centers may also see growth, as they adapt to the increasing demand for electric vehicles and the specific needs of Cybertruck owners. Collaboration between Tesla and local educational institutions for training and research could foster innovation and skill development in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;challenges-and-concerns&quot;&gt;Challenges and Concerns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While excitement surrounds the Cybertruck’s arrival, there are challenges and concerns to address. The unique design of the Cybertruck may require adaptations in service infrastructure. The continued expansion of charging stations will be crucial to support new Cybertruck owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the state’s readiness to embrace this new technology in terms of regulations, safety standards, and public perception may shape the Cybertruck’s success in Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cybertruck’s arrival in Missouri is more than a new vehicle entering the market; it’s a symbol of the ongoing shift toward sustainable transportation and a new chapter in the state’s proud automotive history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The success of the Cybertruck in Missouri will depend on various factors, including consumer acceptance, infrastructure development, and collaboration between Tesla and local stakeholders. However, the excitement and anticipation surrounding this futuristic vehicle suggest that the Show-Me State is ready to embrace the Cybertruck as a part of its automotive future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coleslaw_333/status/1691828028114976903&quot;&gt;Picture Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 20:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-missouri</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-missouri</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
        <category>Missouri</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Cybertruck.dev! Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photo courtesy of Ed Runnion)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/first-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/first-post</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
