<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cybertruck.dev - A Tesla Cybertruck Dev Site! </title>
    <description>A Cybertruck Dev page!</description>
    <link>https://cybertruck.dev/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://cybertruck.dev/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 17:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 17:44:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to tell your Cybertruck Order Number Position</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So you’ve ordered a Cybertruck, and you’re wondering how many people are ahead of you in line.  Here’s how to tell:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tesla.com/cybertruck&quot;&gt;Tesla’s Cybertruck Order Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “Manage” in the upper right corner&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “View Details” next to your Cybertruck order&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “View Order Agreement”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Search for “Order Number” in the document&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Your order number will be in the format RN123456789&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what does that tell you? Not a whole lot without a little more info, so here you go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a &lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/view/tesla-reservation-tracker&quot;&gt;Cybertruck Reservation Tracker&lt;/a&gt;, it will provide you some info, but the value is limited because some of the data is just flat out wrong. My order for example, says it is attached to someone in Ithaca, NY and is a prior Tesla Owner. I am in Missouri, and have never owned a Tesla.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That tracker shows that my order is estimated to be position 6,368, and 1,338 in line for the Trim (3 motor) that I ordered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are also a bunch of duplicate order numbers in there with all sorts of different order dates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So trying to throw out most of their filtering logic based on the assumption that they simply don’t have the right info, let’s start with a more basic assumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Order number 112,744,133 shows up with a “corrected” position of 9, so let’s assume that the order number is within 13-15 numbers of that actual order number, so somewhere around 112,744,120. That puts my order number around 7,080.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tracker tries to estimate out how many “other” orders (other models, not truck) were placed for Teslas in between when the initial order was placed, and my Cybertruck order was placed. I have a hard time believing that many, if any, were ordering other Teslas in the few minutes from the time the order window opened to the time that I ordered, so I would lean towards somewhere in that 7k range for my order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the question is how many folks will cancel their Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many people have already cancelled their Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many people will simply not respond when the order banks actually open up and people need to start configuring the paying for their Cybertruck?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we near the end of Q3 2023, my uneducated assumptions tell me that we will see some pricing and delivery of the Cybertruck before the end of September 2023, and from there we will see production ramp up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am expecting to get to place my order sometime in late Spring 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all based on a lot of assumptions. My last vehicle order, a Ford F250, took 400 days from the day I ordered it to the date I picked it up, and that wasn’t a NEW model, it was just a super duty truck from Ford….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When do you think you’ll get your Cybertruck order?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 08:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-ordernumber</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-ordernumber</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Cybertruck's Arrival in Missouri - A New Chapter in Automotive Innovation</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-cybertrucks-arrival-in-missouri-a-new-chapter-in-automotive-innovation&quot;&gt;The Cybertruck’s Arrival in Missouri: A New Chapter in Automotive Innovation&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missouri, long known for its contributions to the automotive industry, is soon to become one of the latest states to welcome Tesla’s futuristic electric vehicle, the Cybertruck. Set to disrupt the trucking market with its radical design and cutting-edge technology, the Cybertruck is poised to make a significant impact in the Show-Me State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;teslas-cybertruck-a-quick-overview&quot;&gt;Tesla’s Cybertruck: A Quick Overview&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cybertruck, announced by Tesla in 2019, is a fully electric pickup truck that challenges the conventional automotive design. With its angular, stainless steel exterior and innovative electric drivetrain, the Cybertruck has captured the imagination of auto enthusiasts and tech-savvy consumers alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featuring a 100 cubic feet of exterior, lockable storage, the Cybertruck aims to provide utility and performance without compromising on environmental sustainability. With different models offering a range of up to 500 miles on a single charge and the ability to tow over 14,000 pounds, it is seen as a serious competitor to traditional fossil fuel-powered trucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;missouris-automotive-history&quot;&gt;Missouri’s Automotive History&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Missouri has a rich history in the automotive industry. Kansas City and St. Louis have been home to several major car manufacturing plants, contributing significantly to the economy and technological development in the area. The arrival of the Cybertruck is seen as a continuation of this tradition, marking a new era of innovation and progress in automotive manufacturing and electric vehicle adoption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-demand-for-electric-vehicles-in-missouri&quot;&gt;The Demand for Electric Vehicles in Missouri&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In recent years, Missouri has seen a growing interest in electric vehicles (EVs). The state government has been proactive in supporting EV adoption through incentives, charging infrastructure, and collaboration with industry leaders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the Cybertruck’s arrival, there is anticipation for a surge in consumer interest in electric trucks, particularly among those involved in agriculture, construction, and other industries that rely heavily on pickup trucks. The Cybertruck’s blend of power and efficiency is expected to appeal to a wide range of consumers across the state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;economic-impact&quot;&gt;Economic Impact&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The introduction of the Cybertruck to Missouri may also have significant economic implications. Beyond the consumer market, the Cybertruck may find applications in various commercial sectors, potentially generating new business opportunities and jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Local dealerships and service centers may also see growth, as they adapt to the increasing demand for electric vehicles and the specific needs of Cybertruck owners. Collaboration between Tesla and local educational institutions for training and research could foster innovation and skill development in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;challenges-and-concerns&quot;&gt;Challenges and Concerns&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While excitement surrounds the Cybertruck’s arrival, there are challenges and concerns to address. The unique design of the Cybertruck may require adaptations in service infrastructure. The continued expansion of charging stations will be crucial to support new Cybertruck owners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the state’s readiness to embrace this new technology in terms of regulations, safety standards, and public perception may shape the Cybertruck’s success in Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Cybertruck’s arrival in Missouri is more than a new vehicle entering the market; it’s a symbol of the ongoing shift toward sustainable transportation and a new chapter in the state’s proud automotive history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The success of the Cybertruck in Missouri will depend on various factors, including consumer acceptance, infrastructure development, and collaboration between Tesla and local stakeholders. However, the excitement and anticipation surrounding this futuristic vehicle suggest that the Show-Me State is ready to embrace the Cybertruck as a part of its automotive future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/coleslaw_333/status/1691828028114976903&quot;&gt;Picture Source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 20:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-missouri</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/cybertruck-missouri</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
        <category>Missouri</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Cybertruck.dev! Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Photo courtesy of Ed Runnion)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>https://cybertruck.dev/first-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://cybertruck.dev/first-post</guid>
        
        
        <category>Tesla</category>
        
        <category>Cybertruck</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
